[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 23]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
“Unsoiled Starlight” ]
[Original Writer: Shan Gu Jun]
Want me to give you a ride?
No need.
I'm going to Yunteng Technology
for outside business today.
The car I called is downstairs.
This is an independent project
I fought hard to get.
Good luck.
I'll pick you up when it's over.
You know,
we've been working on this
home robot project
for 5 years.
It's like our own child.
If the funding chain hadn't broken,
I wouldn't bear to transfer it
to someone else.
Look—
this kind of
high-end smart technology,
its prospects are obvious to everyone.
Understood.
We'll conduct a comprehensive evaluation
of the project.
We'll need Mr. Du's full cooperation then.
We've already reached a consensus
with Mr. Gao of Lisen Home.
We're asking you to do
the legal assessment
just as a formality.
No need to be so serious.
Procedures are necessary
and indispensable.
We'll verify truthfully.
Please rest assured.
It recharges me.
What?
Are they hard to deal with?
Clients are always hard to deal with.
Not really.
I'm pretty easy to deal with.
True.
Known in the industry for
being hard to deal with—
the boss of Zhuoyuan Tech—
was handled by me.
I even admire myself.
Then—
reward me.
Drive.
[Yunteng Tech Legal Assessment Report]
Mr. Du.
You sit. I have things to do.
Go ahead.
Sis, I'm taking it.
Okay.
[Yunteng Tech Legal Assessment Report]
Hello.
What business are you here for?
Yes.
Is the main hall closed now?
The property rights center
is under renovation.
Go out and turn right.
There's a temporary counter .
Okay.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
Here.
Thanks.
Hello.
The security guard inside said
this temporary counter
can handle business.
Right?
Yes.
Our center is under renovation.
We're very sorry.
What project do you want to check?
This is an authorization letter
from Yunteng Tech.
I'd like to check
the company's intellectual
property registration.
Okay.
One moment, please.
[Senzhou Municipal Intellectual
Property Bureau]
[Intellectual Property
Registration Certificate]
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[Hongzheng Law Firm]
[Xiao Junhua]
How's the progress on Yunteng's side?
Mr. Du isn't very cooperative.
But for now,
the procedures and materials are complete.
There shouldn't be any problems.
Well done.
[Attorney Shu Tinglan]
[Yunteng Technology] [Risam furniture]
[Family robot patent transfer ceremony]
[1. List of Technical Materials Handover]
[2. Acceptance Confirmation Form]
here's to working together.
Here's to working together.
[Yunteng Technology] [Lisen Home]
[Patent Transfer Ceremony
for Household Robot Technology]
Lawyer Xiao.
So is this case
considered closed?
It's only officially closed
after payment is made.
But it should be soon.
About a week.
Lisen will pay Yunteng.
We just need to wait.
Let's go eat.
No.
Looks like today
I need to get home early.
Okay.
Go.
[One week later]
Good morning.
Morning.
Tinglan.
Something's happened with
the Yunteng project.
The technical patent contract
for Lisen's acquisition
has a problem.
What did you say?
That contract
has no legal effect whatsoever.
Tinglan.
Such a huge problem,
causing the client to lose over 2 million,
and damaging the firm's reputation—
this is your failure, Xiao Junhua.
By the end of today,
you must give me an answer.
Okay, Mr. Zhao.
If this problem isn't solved,
I resign.
Where are you going?
To Yunteng.
If you go now,
what can you find?
This project—
I failed to check it properly for you.
I also have an inescapable responsibility.
No matter what,
this is the project I led.
I must see it through to the end.
Excuse me,
could you go a bit faster?
Okay.
[Zhuo Yu'an]
Hello?
Working overtime today?
Yea.
Something came up at the firm.
I'll be home late.
Want me to come pick you up?
No need.
Then you—
be safe on the road.
Let me know when you arrive.
Okay.
Secretary Wang.
Where's Mr. Du?
Lawyer Shu.
Mr. Du resigned.
Resigned?
Isn't he Yunteng's second-
largest shareholder?
How could he resign?
Mr. Du absconded with the funds.
You mean—
the patent transfer fee?
Yes.
I heard he used his position
to sell patents that weren't his
to the acquiring party.
Now that it's exposed,
he's taken the money and run.
I've got something on.
Gotta go.
Secretary Wang—
Sorry.
The number you have dialed is powered off.
You're back.
I was worried about you.
I'm fine.
I'm here.
Am I useless?
Careful, it's hot.
I've carefully reviewed all the materials.
There are no problems.
When you obtained the
certification documents,
was there anything unusual?
Although Du Yunteng
wasn't very cooperative,
he gave me all the materials
he was supposed to.
Could it be
that the authorization letter?
What's wrong with it?
I just remembered—
that day, when I mentioned
intellectual property ownership,
he got a bit emotional.
We've already reached a consensus
with Mr. Gao of Lisen Home.
We're asking you to do
the legal assessment
just as a formality.
No need to be so serious.
Could it be
that the property rights aren't his?
Later, when I went to the property
rights center to verify,
the first time, I couldn't find it.
The second time,
they said it was under renovation.
A security guard told me
there was a temporary counter
that could handle business.
This property rights certificate
was printed at the temporary window
on the second floor.
[Senzhou Municipal Intellectual
Property Bureau]
[Intellectual Property
Registration Certificate]
Hello.
What business are you here for?
The property rights center
is under renovation.
Go out and turn right. There's a
temporary window.
Okay.
Thank you.
No problem.
Renovation.
Temporary counter.
The window was fake.